Guide to the Gee Family Association papers MS 1018
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Gee Family Association papers
1986-2018
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Gee Family Association
MS 1018
1 Linear Feet
The Gee Family Association (GFA) is an organization of generations of Gees and their extended families. This collection includes print materials such as event flyers and programs, genealogies, and circa 20 photographs, primarily regarding the activities of the Gee Family Association in Houston, Texas.
Biographical / Historical
The Gee Family Association (GFA) is an organization of generations of Gees and their extended families. The GFA has chapters in several major U.S. cities. Each year, the Houston organization gathers at two major events, a Chinese New Year Banquet, a family picnic, as well as varying activities in between. The GFA hosts an annual Chinese New Year Dinner which celebrates special achievements, recognition of family member births, graduates, marriages, and elders, Gee pioneer families, and the Gee Education Fund Scholarships. Through these gatherings, genealogical information is exchanged, family news is shared, and cultural traditions are maintained. [Exceprted from GFA brochure, 2019.]
Content Description
Print materials such as event flyers and programs, genealogies, and circa 20 photographs, primarily regarding the activities of the Gee Family Association in Houston, Texas.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Andrew Gee on behalf of the Gee Family Association, in 2022.
Index Terms
Subjects
Education; Asian Americans; Genealogy
Document Types
photographs; letters (correspondence); brochures; clippings (information artifacts); newsletters; family papers
Places
Texas -- Houston
- Series I: Gee Family Association
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gee Family Association roast of Harry Gee. Jr., 1995-02-25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Gee Family Association annual activities, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gee Family Association annual Chinese New Year Brochures, 1991-2019 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CAFA & GFA Annual Picnic at Safari Texas Ranch activities, 2005-2013 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gee Family Association invoices & checks/checkbooks (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Gee Family Association donations/endowment papers (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gee Family Association thank you cards & various corresponding envelopes (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gee Family Association miscellaneous papers (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Gee Family Association no date correspondences (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Legion, Department of Texas - American Chinese Post 596 Compliment (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Senate of the State of Texas Proclamation No. 296, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Zhi Yang Monthly Magazines, 1995-2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Series II: Gee Family history documents
  - Gee Family Genealogy/History (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gee Family History Book Supporting Items (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Gee Family Floral Arrangements/Photographs (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Various Gee Family member news clippings (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Diana Gee Olympics, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Harry Gee Jr. Letters/Young Chinese Leaders Forum, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)